Fear thy neighbor.
The Crazies is a mystery, horror, action film directed by Breck Eisner.
Four friends find themselves trapped in their small hometown after they discover
their friends and neighbors going quickly and horrifically insane.
David, played by Timothy Olyphant.
Judy, played by Radha Mitchell.
Russell, played by Joe Anderson.
Becca, played by Danielle Panabaker.
Pvt. Billy Babcock, played by Joe Reegan.
Intelligence Officer, played by Glenn Morshower.
The Crazies is a 2010 science fiction horror film that is
a remake of the 1973 film The Crazies.
It stars Timothy Olyphant, Radha Mitchell, Joe Anderson, and Danielle Panabaker as residents of a fictional Iowa
town that becomes afflicted by a biological agent that turns those infected into violent killers.
It is directed by Breck Eisner based on a
screenplay by Scott Kosar and Ray Wright.
Romero, who wrote and directed the original, served as an executive producer.
The film was released on February 26, 2010, and grossed
$54 million on a $20 million budget.
It received mixed reviews according to Metacritic, with the critical summary on Rotten
Tomatoes calling the film "tense, nicely shot, and uncommonly intelligent".
The film explores themes of biological weapon,
cover-up, remake, madness, psychosis.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.